Contact

2066342841 (Mobile) nathaniel.reister@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/natereister (LinkedIn) natereister.com (Portfolio)

github.com/Nathaan92 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Public Speaking
Political Science
Community Development

Languages

English

Nathaniel Reister

A Full Stack Developer with more than 8 years in management. I am adept at meeting expectations and achieving goals.

Seattle

Summary

A Graduate from SUNY Brockport with a Bachelors in Communications and Political Science as well as a Graduate from The Tech Academies Full Stack Developer Program. I am a bit of a traveler having moved to and from homes in New York, California, and now Washington. I've had the opportunity of a diverse history having worked in set shops in NYC, building homes in Long Island, studying in Rochester, and managing building projects in Seattle. I have dedicated my last year to becoming a Full Stack Developer and after having completed 6 weeks of internship I am confident that I have the skills necessary to be a major asset to your team.

Experience

BELOTTI MCHUGH DESIGN & CONSTRUCTION SERVICES

Construction Superintendent

June 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Seattle, Washington, United States

Management of Commercial, High End Residential, Multi-family, and Remodel Construction Projects in the greater Seattle area.

Prosper I.T. Consulting
Software Developer
October 2020 - December 2020 (3 months)

Remote

During my internship I had participated in 3 sprints over 6 weeks, working with teams ranging from 4 members to just myself. This experience taught me first hand how to employ the methodologies of agile and scrum all while working remotely.

The first was a two week sprint in which I used Django frame work to build a webapp. The purpose of this app was to collect user information on preferences collected from search and survey results to provide them suggestions on what kind of hikes they would be interested in. I utilized Python

for the logic of the program and used CSS and HTML for the construction of the UI.

The second was a four week sprint in which I completed stories for an already developed MVC webpage. This was a particularly fun experience for me in which I not only debugged, developed more striking UI, created another aspect of the webpage but I also delve into a dynamic team environment where we worked on rather complex and new issues. I particularly enjoyed this portion of the experience and found that MVC is a framework that I am comfortable with.

Check out my GitHub for more information on my work!

Fern and Hammer

Owner

October 2016 - June 2018 (1 year 9 months)

Seattle, Washington, United States

Owned and operated a Construction Company that focused on high end Residential Remodels in the Queen Ann neighborhood in Seattle.

Ready Set Inc

Set Builder

October 2015 - July 2016 (10 months)

New York, New York, United States

Custom set Builder for various events, both public and private, held throughout NYC.

Brockport Student Goverment

Cheif Justice

August 2013 - May 2015 (1 year 10 months)

Act in full capacity of a Justice in Brockport Student government, to oversee the operations of the Judicial Branch, and ensure the procedural fairness of Brockport Student Government.

SUNY Brockport ResLIfe

Resident Assistant

August 2013 - May 2015 (1 year 10 months)

SUNY Brockport

While serving in this position I supervised residents and enforce rule and policies of the college.

I created and implement team and community building programming for residents. Managed emergency situations and coordinated with emergency services acting as a first responder and collaborated with on campus organizations to fill resident's needs and concerns.

Southampton Police Department Summer Traffic Control Officer June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months)

In this role my responsibilities included maintaining Southampton Village traffic flow, enforcing village and state laws, ensuring the safety of the general public, reporting any and all major safety concerns to SHPD dispatch, acting a public representative for Southampton Police Dept., and maintaining clear communication with Direct Supervisors and PD.

Education

The Tech Academy

Certificate, Full Stack Development · (2020 - 2020)

State University of New York College at Brockport Bachelor's Degree, Commucication Studies and Political Science · (2012 - 2015)

Temecula Preparatory School (2004 - 2011)